(melodic piano music)
No matter the distance, no matter how
years turn, love takes
flight with a promise of return.
It circles the world, it knows where to
land, still warm in the touch of a
welcoming hand. Boomerang of
love, a flight never lost, through
shadows and storms, it still makes its
course. Each time it is cast, it will
rise far above, returning
again, the boomerang of
love.
Return, oh boomerang, to hearts that are
warm, to the unloved, the
gentle, the kind in the storm. And
above all, return with the truth from
above, to restore what was given,
return as love. Boomerang of
love, a flight never lost, through
shadows and storms, it still makes its
course. Each time it is cast, it will
rise far above, returning
again, the boomerang of
love.
Through the arc of the sky and the breadth
of the
earth, love finds the lost and
rekindles their worth. No force can
deter, no shadow can
stain, the path of love's promise will
find its own way.
Boomerang of love, a flight never
lost, through shadows and storms, it
still makes its course. Each time it is
cast, it will rise far above,
returning again, the boomerang
of
love.
Forever it circles, forever it
flies, beneath the sun, through
unending skies. Boomerang of
love, in its endless return, the
fire keeps glowing, the heart to
ever
burn.